Chapter 39. First night watch for top.
Stub soulless and mending a brace.
Ha ha ha him. Clear my throat.
I've been thinking over it ever since, and that haha is the final consequence.
Why so? Because a laugh's the wisest, easiest answer to all that's queer, and
come what will, one's comforts always left. That unfailing comfort is, it's
all predestinated. I heard not all his talk with Starbucks, though. But to my
poor eye, Starbucks then looked something as I the other evening felt.
Be sure the old mogul had fixed him, too. I twigged it, knew it, had had the
gift might readily have prophesied it.
For when I clapped my eye upon his skull, I saw it. Well, Stub, wise Stub,
that's my title. Well, Stub, what of it, Stub? Here's a carcass. I know not all
that may be coming, but be it what it will, I'll go to it laughing. Such a
waggish learing as lurks in all your horribles. I feel funny. Fa lra skira.
And what's my juicy little pair at home doing now? Crying its eyes out. Giving a
party to the last arrived harpineers. I dare say gay as a frigot's penant. And
so am I. Fa liascara. Oh, we'll drink tonight with hearts as light to love as
gay as fleeting. As bubbles that swim on beaker's brim and break on the lips
while meeting a brave stave that who calls Mr. Starbucks. I I sir aside he's
my superior. He has his too if I'm not mistaken. I I sir just through with this
job coming.